Guide to the Tony Judt Papers MC 233
New York University Archives
- Series I: Books
  - Subseries I: Postwar (2005)
    - Sub-subseries i: Outline Notes, undated
      - 10N: East: Repression, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - 10P: West: Defusion & Polarization, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - 11A: Oil Crisis, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - 11B: Financial Crisis, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - 11C: Economic Downturn, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - 11C: Economic Downturn, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - 11D: Soc-Ec Consequences & Strikes, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - 11E: Lead Years: Italy, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - 11F: Lead Years: Germany, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - 11G: 'Troubles', undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - 11G: 'Troubles', undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - 11H: Post-Everything Ideas, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
      - 11J: 1970s Culture, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - 12A: Feminism, undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - 12A: Feminism, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - 12A: Feminism, undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - 12A: Feminism, undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - 12B: Greens 1A, 1B, 1C, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - 12C: New Politics 3, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - 12D: Eurocommunism 4, 4A, undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - 12E: Ostpolitik (empty), undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - 12F: Helsinki 8, 9, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - 12G: Spain 20-21, undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - 12H: Portugal, undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - 13A: Problems of the Welfare State 2C, undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - 13B: Thatcher & Great Britain 5, 5A, undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - 13C: Mitterrand & France 10-->13, undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - 13C: Mitterrand & France 10-->13, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
      - 13D: Privatisations 7-->7#, undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
      - 13D: Privatisations 7-->7#, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
      - 13E: End of Master Narratives 14A --> 14L, undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
      - 13F: Rights 15A-->19A, undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
      - 14X: Variations Among EE Regimes 22-27, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - 15A: New Cold War, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - 15A: New Cold War, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - 15A: New Cold War, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - 15A: New Cold War, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - 16A: 1989 in Poland (empty), undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - 16B: 1989 in Germany (empty), undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - 16C: 1989 in E. Europe (empty), undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - 16D: 1989 in Baltics (empty), undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - 16E: 1989: Interpretations (empty), undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - 17A: German Unification (empty), undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - 17B: Retributions?, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - 17B: Retributions?, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - 17C: Post-Communist Politics, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - 17C: Post-Communist Politics, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - 17D: Post-Communist Economies, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - 18A: EU, Euro & Expansion, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - 18A: EU, Euro & Expansion, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - 18A: EU, Euro & Expansion, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - 18B: Belgium, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - 18C: Italy, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - 18D: Spain, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - 18F: Czechoslovakia, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - 18H: Yugoslavia, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - 18H: Yugoslavia, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - 18X: Other Fissiles, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - 19A: Globalisation and the State, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - 19B: Corruption and Reforms, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - 19C: The End of Work, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - 19D: The Excluded: social demogr., undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - 19D: The Excluded: social demogr., undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - 19E: The Excluded: Politics, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - 19F: 'Third Way?', undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - 20B: End of European 'Model'?, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - 21E: Postwar amnesias: W. Europe, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - 21F: Postwar amnesias: Germany, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - 21F: Postwar amnesias: Germany, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Introduction and Preface, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Ch. 21 Addenda, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Completed Epilogue Material, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Completed Epilogue Material, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Completed Epilogue Material, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Completed Epilogue Material, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Ch. 10 notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Ch. 11 notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Additional notes (1 of 2), undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - Additional notes (2 of 2), undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - German Unification, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Soviet Break-Up '89-'91, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Baltics '89-'91, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Sub-subseries ii: Subject Notes
      - Thoughts and Quotes, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - General Histories, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - General Histories, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - General Histories, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - General Histories, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - General Histories, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Refugees and Migration, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Refugees and Migration, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Welfare/Social Issues, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - EU, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - EU, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - France, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Spain, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Spain, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Germany, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Germany, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Germany, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Germany, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Germany, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Scandinavia, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Neths, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Portugal (empty), undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - Austria, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Switzerland, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Belgium, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Italy, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - Italy, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - UK, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - UK, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - UK, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - Draft proposal, 1998, undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
      - Suez, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
      - Retribution, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
      - Immediate Post-War, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
      - Legacy of War, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
      - Marshall Plan, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
      - Marshall Plan, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
      - 1968, undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
      - Colonies, undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
      - 1989, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
      - Culture, undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
      - Fashion/Style, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
      - Retribution, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
      - Retribution, undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
      - Retribution, undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
      - Retribution, undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
      - Retribution, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
      - Thoughts and Quotes, undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
      - Division, undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
      - Division, undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
      - Exhaustion?, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Exhaustion?, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Exhaustion?, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Exhaustion?, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Exhaustion?, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Intellectuals and Ideas, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Intellectuals and Ideas, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Cold War, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Cold War, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Cold War, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Cold War, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Chronologies, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Chronologies, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Chronologies, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Proposal material, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Proposal material, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Proposal material, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Proposal material, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Proposal material, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Holocaust, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Memory, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Economics, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Economics, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Economics, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Economics, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Economics, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Intellectuals and Ideas, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Intellectuals and Ideas, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - Cinema, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Europe-America, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Urbanism/Town-planning, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - NATO, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - Maps and Geography, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Education, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - Eastern Europe, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Eastern Europe, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - Greece and Balkans (not Yug), undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Yugoslavia, undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - USSR/Russia, undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - USSR/Russia, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - USSR/Russia, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
      - Poland, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - Baltics, undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - Ukraine, undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Hungary, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Czechoslovakia, undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Excerpts from Economic History of Eastern Europe, Vol. 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Excerpts from Economic History of Eastern Europe, Vol. 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - Excerpts from Economic History of Eastern Europe, Vol. 3, undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - Excerpts from Economic History of Eastern Europe, Vol. 3, undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Sub-subseries iii: Chapter Drafts, undated
      - Chapter 1, undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - Chapter 1, undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - Chapter 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - Chapter 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - Chapter 3, undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - Chapter 4, undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
      - Chapter 5, undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
      - Chapter 6, undated (Box 7, Folder 58)
      - Chapter 6, undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
      - Chapter 7, undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - Chapter 7, undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - Chapter 8, undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
      - Chapter 8, undated (Box 7, Folder 63)
      - Chapter 9, undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
      - Chapter 10, undated (Box 7, Folder 65)
      - Chapter 10, undated (Box 7, Folder 66)
      - Chapter 11, undated (Box 7, Folder 67)
      - Chapter 11, undated (Box 7, Folder 68)
      - Chapter 11, undated (Box 7, Folder 69)
      - Chapter 12, undated (Box 7, Folder 70)
      - Chapter 12, undated (Box 7, Folder 71)
      - Chapter 13, undated (Box 7, Folder 72)
      - Chapter 13, undated (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Chapter 13, undated (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Chapter 13, undated (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Chapter 14, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Chapter 14, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Chapter 15, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Chapter 15, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 16, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 17, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 17, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Chapter 18, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 18, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Chapter 19, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - New Chapter 17, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - New Chapter 18, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Sub-subseries iv: Other Notes and Drafts
      - "From the House of the Dead", undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - "From the House of the Dead", undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Reading lists, circa 1992 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Reading lists, circa 1992 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Reading lists, circa 1992 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Reading lists, circa 1992 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Reading lists, circa 1992 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Reading topics, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Sub-subseries v: Master Set 1st Madeup - Author's Galleys, 20 July 2005
      - Intro, Preface, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Chapter 1, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Chapter 2, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Chapter 3, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Chapter 4, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - Chapter 5, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - Chapter 6, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Chapter 7, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Coda, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Chapter 8, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Chapter 9, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Chapter 10, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Postscript, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - Chapter 11, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Chapter 12, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Chapter 13, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - Chapter 14, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - Chapter 15, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - Chapter 16, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - Chapter 17, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - Chapter 18, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - Chapter 19, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - Chapter 20, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - Chapter 21, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      - Chapter 22, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 45)
      - Chapter 23, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 46)
      - Chapter 24, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - Epilogue, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Sub-subseries vi: Author's correx to final pass, 2005 August 2
      - Misc. corrections, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 49)
      - Misc. corrections, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 50)
      - Misc. corrections, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Sub-subseries vii: "Setting MS" manuscript, 2005
      - Preface, Introduction, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      - Chapter 1, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      - Chapter 2, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      - Chapter 3, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - Chapter 4, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - Chapter 5, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 57)
      - Chapter 6, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 58)
      - Chapter 7, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 59)
      - Coda, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Chapter 8, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Chapter 9, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 62)
      - Chapter 10, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - Chapter 11, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - Chapter 12, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - Chapter 13, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 66)
      - Chapter 14, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - Chapter 15, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - Chapter 16, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 69)
      - Chapter 17, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 70)
      - Chapter 18, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Chapter 19, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Chapter 19, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Chapter 20, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 21, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 22, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 22, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Chapter 23, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 24, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Epilogue (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Sub-subseries viii: Press, reviews, correspondence
      - Reviews, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Reviews, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Reviews, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Reviews, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Reviews, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Reviews, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Reviews, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Reviews, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Reviews, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Reviews, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Reviews, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Reviews, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Reviews, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Reviews, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - Reviews, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Reviews, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Reviews, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - Book Awards, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence returned Jan. 2006 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence returned March 2006 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence returned March 2006 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence returned May-August 2006 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence returned October 2006 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Subseries J: Reappraisals (2008)
    - "Israel book", 2006 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - "Israel book" manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - "Israel book" manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - "Israel book" manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - "Israel book" manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - "Israel book" manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - "Israel book" manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - "Israel book" manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - "Israel book" manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - "Intro to Essay Collection" ( States of Exception), circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - "Intro to Essay Collection" ( States of Exception), circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - "Intro to Essay Collection" ( States of Exception), circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - "Intro to Essay Collection" ( States of Exception), circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - "Intro to Essay Collection" ( States of Exception), circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - "Intro to Essay Collection" ( States of Exception), circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - "Intro to Essay Collection" ( States of Exception), circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - "Intro to Essay Collection" ( States of Exception), circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - "Intro to Essay Collection" ( States of Exception), circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - "Intro to Essay Collection" ( States of Exception), circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - "Intro to Essay Collection" ( States of Exception), circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - "Intro to Essay Collection" ( States of Exception), circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - "Intro to Essay Collection" ( States of Exception), circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - "Intro to Essay Collection" ( States of Exception), circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - introduction draft, undated (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - introduction draft, undated (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - "Essays" manuscript - essays 1-5, undated (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - "Essays" manuscript - essays 6-12, undated (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - "Essays" manuscript - essays 13-18, undated (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - "Essays" manuscript - essays 19-24, undated (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - "Essays" manuscript - essays 25-28, undated (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - "Essays" manuscript - additional pieces, undated (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - "Essays" manuscript - additional pieces, undated (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Article drafts with notes, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Article drafts with notes, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Article drafts with notes, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Article drafts with notes, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Article drafts with notes, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Article drafts with notes, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Article drafts with notes, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Article drafts with notes, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Article drafts with notes, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Article drafts with notes, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Article drafts with notes, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Article drafts with notes, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter I, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter II, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter III, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter IV, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter V, VI, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter VII, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter VIII, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter IX, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter X, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter XI, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter XII, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter XIII, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter XIV, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter XV, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter XVI, XVII, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter XVIII, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter XIX, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter XX, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter XXI, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Draft manuscript - Chapter XXII, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Draft manuscript - Envoi, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Review printouts, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Subseries K: Thinking the Twentieth Century (2012)
    - Tim Snyder (draft), undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Tim Snyder (draft), undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Tim Snyder (draft), undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Tim Snyder (draft), undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Tim Snyder (draft), undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Subseries L: Ill Fares the Land (2010)
    - Reviews, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Subseries M: The Memory Chalet (2010)
    - Review, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Series II: Articles/Essays
  This series is divided into two subseries. Reprints of Judt's articles have been separated from his notes and other source material for articles. The articles are arranged chronologically by publication year.
  This series is comprised primarily of the notes, research, drafts and correspondence related to articles and essays published in a variety of outlets. While this series is extensive in the number of Judt's articles it covers, for some of these works, only photocopies can be found in the collection.
  The following abbreviations are used to denote publication titles:
  FT - Financial Times
  LRB - London Review of Books
  NYR - New York Review of Books
  NYT - New York Times
  TLS - Times Literary Supplement
  TNR - The New Republic
  - Subseries A: Notes, Drafts and Research
    - "What is Left of the Left?" drafts, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - "What is Left of the Left?" drafts, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - "Stalinism in Czechoslovakia", undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Review of The End of the Old Order in Rural Europe, Social History, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Review of The Jews in Modern France, circa 1985 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Review of Essays on France and French Historians by John Stuart Mill, circa 1985 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Review of Intellectuels Francais, Intellectuels Hongrois: XIII-XX siecles, circa 1985 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - "Revolutionary Ends", review of 5 books on 19th century France, notes, drafts, TLS, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - "La Guerre est finie?" review of Spanish Front: Writers on the Civil War, circa 1986 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Review of Paris Shopkeepers and the Politics of Resentment, circa 1986 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Review of Keeping Left? Ceres and the French Socialist Party, circa 1986 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Review of The Pletzl of Paris. Jewish immigrant workers in the Belle Epoque, circa 1986 (Box 10, Folder 42)